# Minjung Kim

google scholar minnjung.github.io github.com/minnjung

minjung.kim@vision.snu.ac.kr

317, Bldg 138, 1 Gwanak-ro, Gwanak-gu, Seoul, South Korea

## **Research Interests**

My research interests are in the field of 3D Place Recognition and Visual Localization, especially about (i) understanding the scene from images and point clouds, (ii) dealing with cross-modalities, and (iii) utilizing high-level semantic information for place recognition.

### Education

Integrated M.S./Ph.D. Student in Computer Science and Engineering

Mar. 2018 - Current

- Seoul National University, Seoul, South Korea
- Adviser: Prof. Gunhee Kim (Vision and Learning Laboratory)

#### B.S. in Computer Science and Engineering

Mar. 2014 - Feb. 2018

- Sogang University, Seoul, South Korea
- Cumulative GPA: 3.58 / 4.3 (3.88 / 4.5), Magna Cum Laude

#### **Publications**

| EP2P-Loc: End-to-End 3D Point to 2D Pixel Localization for Large-Scale Visual Localization  Minjung Kim, Junseo Koo, Gunhee Kim                       | ICCV, 2023<br>(Submitted) |
|---|---------------------------|
| Indoor/Outdoor Transition Recognition Based on Door Detection<br>Seohyun Jeon, <b>Minjung Kim</b> , Seunghwan Park, Jaeyoung Lee                      | UR, 2022                  |
| Drop-Bottleneck: Learning Discrete Compressed Representation for Noise-Robust Exploration Jaekyeom Kim, <b>Minjung Kim</b> , Dongyeon Woo, Gunhee Kim | ICLR, 2021                |
| Logo Detection and Recognition Algorithm using YOLO-v3 Model  Minjung Kim, Sungen Kim, Gunhee Kim   | CICS, 2020                |
| Memorization Precedes Generation: Learning Unsupervised GANs with Memory Networks Youngjin Kim, Minjung Kim, Gunhee Kim                               | ICLR, 2018                |

# Work and Research Experiences

| Teaching Assistant                        | 2022-3 SK ML Engineer course  | Nov. 2022 – Dec. 2022   |
|---|---|-------------------------|
| Teaching Assistant                        | KDB AI course   | April. 2022 – May. 2022 |
| Teaching Assistant                        | LG Al core human resource training course   | Feb. 2022               |
| Teaching Assistant                        | Teaching assistant of Topics in Artificial Intelligence at Seoul National University          | Sep. 2020 – Dec. 2020   |
| Teaching Assistant                        | Teaching assistant of IoT·Artificial Intelligence·Big Data (IAB) at Seoul National University | Sep. 2018 – Jun. 2019   |
| Teaching Assistant                        | Teaching assistant of Discrete Mathematics at Seoul National University                       | Mar. 2018 – Jun. 2018   |
| Research Intern                           | Vision and Learning Laboratory at Seoul National University                                   | Jul. 2017 – Feb. 2018   |
| Research Intern                           | Biointelligence Laboratory at Seoul National University                                       | Sep. 2016 – Feb. 2017   |
| Kit Developer<br>- Arduino & Raspberry Pi | MakeWith (Startup)  | Dec. 2016 – Jan. 2017   |

Teaching Assistant Teaching assistant of C & Python language and project design Mar. 2016 – Dec. 2018

at Sogang University

Admission Test Supervisor Sogang University Feb. 2015 – Feb. 2016

# **Projects**

DeepGuider Apr. 2019 – Current

- To develop a navigation guidance system that enables robots to navigate in urban environment without the need of pre-mapping of the environment

- This research project is funded by the government

## Awards and Scholarship

Samsung Humantech Paper Award Feb. 2021

- Samsung Electronics

- Silver Prize in Signal Processing

KSC 2017 Paper Award Feb. 2018

- Korean Institute of Information Scientists and Engineers

- Third Prize

Magna Cum Laude Honor at Sogang University Feb. 2018

Grade Scholarship at Sogang University

Jul. 2017 – Feb. 2018

The  $10^{\mbox{th}}$  Grade, Windows 10 IoT Core & Microsoft Azure for Microsoft IoT Solution Competition

Intership Scholarship at Sogang University Dec. 2016 – Jan. 2017

Apr. 2017

Admission Test Work Scholarship at Sogang University

Nov. 2015 – Nov. 2016

## **Professional Activities**

| 2022-3 SK Engineer Technical Coaching | Feb. 2023     |
|---------------------------------------|---------------|
| Reviewer                              | CVPR, 2023    |
| Reviewer                              | ICLR, 2023    |
| Reviewer                              | ACCV, 2022    |
| Reviewer                              | NeurIPS, 2022 |
| Reviewer                              | ICLR, 2022    |
| Reviewer                              | NeurlPS, 2021 |